The same thing that we are now going through in the
text and I like it when in a book in
complex Tibetan it says the same thing
that I am telling you in simple language if before
history on the fingers and constantly the
abbot of the monastery there, for example, on the
table where I lived there were three thousand
monks and in front of them will stand the
abbot very wise and very powerful
this person has a lot of power what the
abbot says can happen
serious punishments
people respect the abbot
they are kind of a little and even afraid of him and
try to somehow influence him
from the story about how two monks are sitting
next to each other one of them can
read minds and and the abbot
is held to this complex
ceremony and this monk who we
consider thinks of others he looks at
this abbot turn to his
comrade say you know draining our
abbot and he is not a Buddhist
be why and he never took
refuge he still uses
fertilizer
our abbot believes in external objects
they are seeds he tries to become more successful
doing big actions
and doing so
insistently in fact  does not follow the
Buddhist worldview and does not take
refuge.
Once I promised
1,000 people a
line of conservative architects
near Florida,
and these three felts asked me to
speak to them. At that time, there was a
big discussion about whether it is
worth selling oil to China or not,
and we started a conversation. I began at the beginning of
my speech by asking these receptors, “What do
you think, should we submit this to an oil
company in China or with these?” I will
gradually teach them the ropes and the four steps.
Two hours later,
and at the end of the speech, I asked, “What should we
do with energy supplies to the States?”
How can we make
the States have more energy? We need to decide
that we need more energy.
Then what needs to be done? The second step is to
go to some other country
that needs energy, and the third step is to
help the other side get energy.
4. Be happy for this from the start of
production. It’s strange, but then they realized
that this is wonderful. And that’s the moment
when they realized this. These thousands of people
accepted the invitation and became Buddhists.
That’s why sometimes it will not be like
bodies to me, but you won’t become
Buddhists
if  Planted seeds, it means to
you that you still need to plow
the land and what to do in the garden, and the answer is yes, most often you
need to do something until a certain
point. When you can perform miracles, we'll
talk about this later.